Oh.
Ah.
>> [screaming]
>> Oh.
Oh. Wow.
Wow.
How about you?
Huh?
Stop.
What?
Oh.
>> [gasps]
>> Wow.
It's the perfect box. We can make so
many cool things with this.
>> Yeah, like a bouncy house.
>> No, that's silly. We should make a
ballroom. It's classy.
>> What are you talking about? A bouncy
house has so much class.
>> No, it doesn't. It's not even a real
building.
>> You don't even know a thing about
architecture, Panda.
>> Well, you do whatever you want. I'm
going to build my ballroom.
>> Excuse me, I saw the box first. Bouncy
house.
Look what you did. Shame on you.
>> No, no shame on me. You're the one who
ruined the box.
>> Well, you would waste it anyway. Your
idea is horrible.
>> Oh, really? I'm going to make my own
amazing house.
>> But my house will be a quadrillion times
better.
>> Okay, we'll see.
>> Yeah, we will.
I claim this. Grizzly land.
Hey Panda, check out how red my house
is.
Wow. You think that's good? I've got an
elevator. What you got?
>> Swing. Hot tub. Microwave.
>> Observatory.
Beautiful.
Library.
Pulpit.
Paris.
Flat screen.
>> Launch the swirl.
>> Eyebrows. Hey.
What?
>> [snorts]
>> I don't know. It's a little complicated.
Things we said, can I take them all
back?
Memories, [singing]
all fuzzy and faded.
Funny how our dreams [music]
come to an end.
>> [music]
>> So I built a wall around my little
heart. Sometimes things break and they
fall apart, but there's one thing that
I know.
Someday
>> Someday [singing]
>> we will be together again.
>> Together again.
>> Someday I'll hold your hand again.
>> Hold your hand.
>> And look into your eyes and say
that we were
>> We [singing] were never meant
>> Never meant to be apart.
>> We were never meant to
>> If only that moment [music and singing]
was now.
>> If only that day was today.
>> Oh, baby. I'm sorry, baby. Can you find
it in your heart to forgive my soul? I'm
sorry, baby.
>> [snorts]
>> I'm sorry, too. I missed you, guys. I
was so lonely.
Come on.
Let's go tell Panda we're sorry, too.